creafi.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy policy | C4MOnline.com

The user of the **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** website will be able to register as a registered user or as a subscriber of information publications on any of the **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** websites providing certain personal information.

Through this, **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** situated on 26 Ghar Id-Dud Street, Sliema SLM1573, Malta, informs users about all its other different internet portals (from now on "Users" and the "Portal") and about its protection policies of personal information (from now on "Personal Information") so that the Users can determine freely and voluntarily if they want to provide the Personal Information that **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** requires and can access when the Users subscribe to any of the services offered by **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** on or across the Portal. **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** reserves the right to edit the current policy so that it includes new laws and legislations as well as industry practices. In this case, **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** will announce any changes on this page with sufficient prior notice before putting it into practice.

Certain services offered on the portal can contain special conditions with specific precautions regarding data protection. Specifically, they are related to the series of web pages below of which **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** maintains an alliance with the owning company of the websites. This is done in a way in which **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** limits the promotion of the services in order to obtain royalties, but in no case is **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** responsible for the collection of the data, nor other activities protected by legislation that can be carried out. At present, **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** has a series of registered domains whose content is directly aimed at the server of the business who owns the domain in such a way that **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** is not responsible for the management that is carried out.

### Provision of services

Conscious of the importance of protecting the privacy of the users, **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** offers the most confidential and secure service, using the most up to date technology in order to safeguard the privacy of their electronic communication and the personal information that is generated from this. However, despite the fact that this entity has implemented all the methods asked for the different levels of security in order to avoid whatever incident that could effect in the misuse of their information, it is necessary to be aware these methods of security are not impregnable. Therefore **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** will not be responsible for the damage that malicious third parties could do through unauthorized access to the **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** information systems.

### Registration forms and files

When signing up to our services, the Users' personal details will be added to a file corresponding to the type of service requested for which **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** is responsible. This/these file/s have been duly registered with the Malta Agency of Data Protection. The User will declare that they understand and they give their expressed consent so **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** can proceed with the automated handling of the said information. However, this consent can be revoked at any moment by the affected, causing them to be taken off and 'blacklisted' from our system according to the process that will be shown later.

### Handling of Information

Personal information will be subject to handling when it is suitable, pertinent and not excessive, in relation to the field and the purpose for which it has been obtained, in agreement with what has been stipulated in the Official Data Protection Laws. The information that the user has supplied to **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** by means of access to whatever service they require, will be used to determine their area of interest therefore to improve customer satisfaction during the contractual relationship. To do this, we will use their data (their telephone number) which will help to build profiles for our users and therefore help both direct marketing and commercial communications, using the most appropriate methods; SMS/MMS, emails, automatic calls or other manual or automatic tools. The information obtained will be treated with maximum confidentiality, applying the highest security methods.

### Consent

Taking into account what has previously been said, we will assume that consent has been given to the handling of the user's data, as has been stated previously. We remind the user that at any time they can exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation or objection of their information by sending an email with their telephone number, indicating in their application, the word STOP.

### Transfer of information

The user expresses their consent that their personal information can be handed over to other companies in order to send information about various services related to those applied for from **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** The user can revoke their consent at any time and exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation or objection following the process indicated in the paragraph entitled 'Consent' sending a text message with the words STOP TRANSFER. Moreover, we inform the user that their telephone number may be passed on to other Malta or European companies in the direct marketing sector and telephone voice services of added value so they can receive information about new products and services that might interest them. The information would be related (although sometimes indirectly) to the services to which they applied. Users can revoke their consent to companies receiving their information by stopping all services, but titling the message CANCEL SUBSCRIPTION.

When giving Personal Information over third parties, the procedure will be explained to Users in a text message containing the identification of the society who transfers the information and the third party to whom their information will be given, and the type of activities the third party is involved in, including their aims. The User can oppose at any moment to any or all of the predetermined transfers of information by exercising their rights explained in point below.

In accordance to what is stipulated in these laws, in all information sent, the word 'Publicity' will appear in the title, identifying clearly the business to whom the publicity belongs. At any time, the User can opt out of this service by following the process indicated, but using the title CANCEL PUBLICITY.

### Disclaimer

The present disclaimer (from now on "Disclaimer") regulates the use of the internet service portal [Crazy4Media Online.com](http://www.c4monline.com/) (from now on "Website") of **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** with registered address in 26 Ghar ID-DUD Street - Sliema - SLM 1573 (Malta).

### Legislation

Likewise, the use of the Portal is subject to the disclaimers, rules of use and instructions, made available to the User by **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** which are substituted, completed and or modified in the present Disclaimer. Generally, the relationship between **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** and the User of its telecommunication services, via the website, are subject to legislation and Malta jurisdiction.

All legal matters concerning both **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** and the User, about the giving up of privileges are subject to the jurisdiction and exclusive capacity of the Courts and Tribunals of Malta law.

### Use and User Access

The access to any of the products or services in the present Website by the User, is done so under their own responsibility, exonerating **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** of all responsibility. **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** can refuse access to any User from the time of learning that the User isn't complying to the requirements already stated.

The company reserves the right to modify the Website in any way they consider appropriate without previous notice, being able to change, delete the content and the services that are provided, as well as the form in which they appear, and their destination on the servers.

The use of the Portal by the user (from now on "User") implicates the acceptance of each and every one of the regulations included in the version of the disclaimer published by **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** at the time the User accesses the portal. As a consequence, the user must carefully read the present Disclaimer every time it is displayed on the Portal, so as not to be affected by the modifications.

### Industrial and Intellectual Property

The rights of intellectual property of the content of the web pages, their graphic design, and their codes, are owned by **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** and therefore it is prohibited to reproduce, distribute, communicate publicly, transform or do any other activity that can be carried out with the contents of its Web pages, it is also prohibited to quote sources unless written permission is sought from **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.**.

Equally, all commercial names, brands or different logos of whatever class found on the **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** website belong to their designers and are protected by the law.

### Web Content and Links

**Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** will not be held responsible for the misuse of the contents of its Website, this is solely the responsibility of the person who accesses them or uses them.

**Crazy4Media Online Ltd.** does not assume any responsibility for the information contained on the websites of third parties, that can be accessed by links or by search engines when searching for **Crazy4Media Online Ltd.**.
